<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MinorFactionGreenmanTitle">Amblyr</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MinorFactionGreenmanDescription">The Amblyr are a quiet race that has yet to make their mark on the galaxy. Little known, despite the infamy of their most famous citizen, X, they appear to be descended from a species of marine reptile. The Amblyr's homeworld is a humid, swampy planet where the society's most sophisticated cities are algae mega-platforms that drift across the quaggy expanses. With abundant seaweed crops providing the majority of their diet as well as reserves of biofuel, the Amblyr  civilization is a boringly harmonious one focusing on progress and prosperity for all. Dependable, predictable, and placid, it is unsurprising that X made a break for the stars.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassPopulationEmpireAffinityGreenmanTitle">[greenman]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassPopulationStarSystemAffinityGreenmanTitle">Systems with [greenman]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationGreenmanTitle">[greenman]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityGreenmanTitle">Amblyr</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityGreenmanDescription">Peaceful and lethargic, the Amblyr loathe violence and adore most types of seaweed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroGreenman01Title">Rhync Raggiodri, a.k.a. The Photobomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroGreenman01Description">Once a galaxy-wide threat to honest investors and electronic banking systems, the “Photobomber” was captured and offered either power or punishment. A relatively quick thinker, he slightly altered his name and chose to study as a Hero with the plan to repay (most of) his debts. Now a Hero and governor of systems, Rhync has turned his charm and cleverness into crowd-pleasing policies and wily political maneuvers. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroGreenman02Title">Rhync Raggiodri, a.k.a. The Photobomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroGreenman02Description">Once a galaxy-wide threat to honest investors and electronic banking systems, the “Photobomber” was captured and offered either power or punishment. A relatively quick thinker, he slightly altered his name and chose to study as a Hero with the plan to repay (most of) his debts. Officially acquiring the status of Hero, Rhync now works as a leader of ships and fleets, turning his wily thinking into highly effective--if occasionally unorthodox--battle tactics. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAffinityGreenmanTitle">Amblyr</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAffinityGreenmanDescription">[TBD] Amblyr Heroes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-Intro-Title">Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part1)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-Intro-Description">It requires a great deal of structure and order to build ships and execute business across the galaxy, and all of that while handling the affairs of billions of citizens. Precision and control are paramount; without them, things could crumble into chaos--a terrifying thought.
However, there is an agent of chaos loose in the galaxy, a strange being from a little-known species. Known only as the Photobomber, his pranks, thefts, and intrusions are destabilizing financial institutions and police forces on many systems. Every time the law comes close, the Photobomber slips away to appear somewhere else, in a new disguise, peddling new tricks and stealing new treats.
It is time to put an end to this; it is time to impose a bit of order on the Photobomber's worrying activities. The governments of the galaxy have pooled their forces to bring him to justice; whoever manages to pinpoint this slippery character will get the best of the donated rewards.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-Description">Track Him Down!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-Objective">Traces of the Photobombers' activities are numerous; investigate all the marked Curiosities</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-ObjectiveTooltip">The quest will end when all marked Curiosities have been searched, and whoever contributes the most to the effort gets the best reward! Search at least $Amount04Name Curiosities to have a chance at a reward.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest05-Coop-Outcome">There he goes! You almost had him, but it seems that the Photobomber managed to steal an exceedingly fast Hero ship and slip away. Rewards will be given, as promised, but the chase is not over.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Intro-Title">Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part2)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Intro-Description">The Photobomber is on the run, pursued seriously for the first time due to a combined effort of all the galaxy's empires. While there are fewer and fewer places for him to run, he has a very good ship in which to do the running. A stolen Hero hull upgraded with pirate technology and a couple of Mavros flux accelerators, the Photobomber's personal yacht is every bit as slippery as its owner.
The game is afoot!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Description">Find and capture the Photobomber on his personal yacht -- a quick little thing stolen from the Academy!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Objective">Intercept the Photobomber's ship</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-ObjectiveTooltip">Guard or Blockade a system that the Photobomber is passing through. If someone destroys the Photobomber's ship, the quest will fail </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Outcome">Brilliant! A combination of dogged perseverance and dumb luck has given you the prize: The Photobomber and all of his secrets. While compliments and notes of appreciation pour in, the next question is clear. How do we take his advanced--if nefarious--skills, and turn them to the good of the empire?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest10-Compet-Failed">The Photobomber has been captured or killed by another empire. The quest has failed!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignHeroGreenManTitle">Stolen Hero Ship</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-IntroTitle">Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part3)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-IntroDescription">Caught! Like a fish wriggling on the hook, the Photobomber's twists and turns weren't enough to evade your ships. This troublemaker and daredevil is now in your hands, and the question is what to do with him. Intelligent, if sly, and creative, if unprincipled, bringing the criminal into society could put his talents to good use.
Rehabilitation is the answer, the Photobomber is quick to accept any alternative to hard labor on a rocky asteroid. He claims to regret the error of his ways, and is even willing to work to help pay back galactic society for all the trouble he has caused. Let us hope that there is no backsliding!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01Title">Honorable Admiral</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01Description">If his change of heart is sincere, somebody that calculating and clever might make a very good admiral. Get him some training at the Academy!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01Objective">Bring the ship to the Academy</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01ObjectiveTooltip">The ship has to orbit or be docked arround the Academy system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01Outcome">Some of the grizzled veterans of the fleet look at Rhynchus with a jaundiced eye, but his knack for coming up with creative solutions and entertaining pranks make him welcome nonetheless. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice01Failed">The quest has failed because the stolen ship has been destroyed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02Title">Potential Governor</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02Description">He can use his creativity as a governor, and keeping him off ships and on a planet might help him keep his promises…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02Objective">Land the ship in one of your Systems' hangars.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02ObjectiveTooltip">The ship has to be in the hangar of one of your Colonies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02Outcome">Given the relative celebrity and notoriety he gained as the Photobomber, Rhynchus is welcomed by the population like a star. Let's hope that he lives up to their expectations--and yours.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest26-Choice02Failed">The quest has failed because the stolen ship has been destroyed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponBeamQuest3Title">Cleaver</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponBeamQuest3Description">This particle weapon damages not only enemy ships but also their crews. Its gruesome nickname is derived from this anti-personnel effect.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestCoop10Title">Reanimator</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestCoop10Description">Though this factory does not really bring the dead back to life, it does provide highly advanced exoskeletons and neural implants that permit the retired, infirm, and elderly to join active duty on the same performance level as their younger peers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventNarrative70Title">Quest: Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part1)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventNarrative71Title">Quest: Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part2)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventNarrative72Title">Quest: Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part3)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventNarrative73Title">Quest: Antihero with a Thousand Faces (Part3)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorGreenmanTitle">Amblyr Citizens</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorGreenmanDescription">+1 [greenman] on your home system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorProfitableExploitationsTitle">Profitable Exploitations</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorProfitableExploitationsDescription">Having mining and drilling operations led by daring, business-oriented supervisors results in extraction facilities turning bigger profits.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorIndustryContactsTitle">Industry Contacts</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitMinorIndustryContactsDescription">A strong network of contacts in various key industriual positions gets things done faster and for a lower price than any standard contractor.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00PopulationCollectionGreenmanTitle">Global Resource Exploitation and Extraction Decree</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00PopulationCollectionGreenmanDescription">The Amblyrs' ability to seemingly put whole sectors of the economy into overdrive appears to be almost innate. By enabling their talents with a little administrative nudge, the raw material yields can skyrocket.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00PopulationCollectionGreenmanShortTitle">Drill Mill Bill</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationCollectionBonusGreenman1">[greenman] Population Collection I</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationCollectionBonusGreenman2">[greenman] Population Collection II</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationCollectionBonusGreenman3">[greenman] Population Collection III</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationCollectionBonusGreenman3_TooltipEffect">Amblyr Law Unlocked</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>