<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter1Title">Basic Fighter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter1Description">Fighters use advanced comm systems to target and destroy enemy ships. They generally go for Bombers (whether they are acting offensively or defensively), but will target other ships if there are no Bombers in range.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter2Title">Advanced Fighter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter2Description">This newer generation of fighter is an improvement, as it uses more advanced (and expensive) materials and takes advantage of improved engine and weapon efficiency.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber1Title">Basic Bomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber1Description">Bombers are designed to target large enemy ships. Their limited range means they will tend to go for what is closer, but have advantages against larger ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber2Title">Advanced Bomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber2Description">Improved Bombers are more dangerous not only for their speed and maneuverability but also for their increasingly lethal paylods, developed with the latest military technology.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter3Strategic3Title">Heavy Fighter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronFighter3Strategic3Description">Sacrificing armor for improved weapon systems, pirate modifications have raised critical damage at the expense of some durability compared to the Advanced Fighter model.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber3Strategic4Title">Light Bomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSquadronBomber3Strategic4Description">By stripping the Advanced Bomber of some protective shielding pirate modifications have made it a little more fragile, but improved its evasion capabilities, while packing the same punch.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSquadronDefenseEnhancer1Strategic3Title">Squadron Shifter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSquadronDefenseEnhancer1Strategic3Description">The antimatter auxiliary engines stocked in this support module are mounted before deployment. They greatly improve durability and dodge capability of squadrons.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSquadronOffenseEnhancer1Strategic4Title">Strike Multiplier</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSquadronOffenseEnhancer1Strategic4Description">These adamantian-enhanced weapons systems are mounted before deployment. They maintain a high level of damage and improve the probability of critical hits.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakEnhancer1Title">Smart Flak</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakEnhancer1Description">By using self-aware individual shards as part of larger explosive devices, pieces of flak can select slightly better paths that increase the probabilitys of impact with enemy projectiles.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakEnhancer1Tooltip">Increases efficiency of the ship's Flak against Missiles &amp; F/Bs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakScrambler1Title">Repulsive Plates</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakScrambler1Description">Cycling powerful, irregularly-timed magnetic fields through the hull, this disposable armor greatly reduces the probability of enemy guns successfully hitting friendly squadrons.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportFlakScrambler1Tooltip">Flak targeting F/Bs of the ship are 50% less effective (does not add up)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignFilterSquadronTitle">Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignFilterSquadronDescription">Show only Squadron ship modules</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatBombersCountDescription">The cumulative number of Bomber units</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatFightersCountDescription">The cumulative number of Fighter units</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-Intro-Title">A Swarm of Locusts</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-Intro-Description">Pirates are rarely at the forefront of new technologies. But this time they have cutting edge military systems, and are producing ships equipped with advanced fighter and bomber squadrons. The carrier ships themselves are not very impressive--re-purposed freighters and cargo vessels--but they are loading them with swarms of small but effective interceptors. These new craft are appearing all over the galaxy, threatening trade, travel, and sentient lives. 
It is time to put rivalries aside, get together, and stamp out this new pirate menace. New tactics and technologies are being used, and whoever takes out more of the pirate fleets is likely to have an edge in learning and adopting them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-Description">Pirates are deploying new ships with fighters and bombers. This threat to galactic order--and your imperial plans--must be stopped.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-Objective">Destroy all the pirate fleets</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-ObjectiveTooltip">The locations of the pirate fleets are indicated on the galactic map. You have to defeat at least $Amount04Name fleets to have a chance to receive a Reward. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest04-Coop-Outcome">Now that the dust has settled and the cheering is over, it's time to figure out how the pirates got their hands on such advanced technology. There is a mystery here, and to prevent another pirate incursion it has to be solved.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Intro-Title">The Power behind the Drones</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Intro-Description">Your experts in techno-xeno-anthropology are unanimous in their opinion: the style, code, engineering quality, and substrates all point to techniques and processes used by the Mavros.
This means that somewhere in the galaxy a hidden research site--well-equipped with both tools and renegade, troublemaking engineers--is selling fighter/bomber technology to anybody who can afford it. Unless this base can be found and this unpleasant business stopped, the Mavros will continue causing trouble for everybody.
On the other hand, engineers who are that clever could be useful if their politics were slightly readjusted... Perhaps a generous bribe--er, signing bonus--could convince them to come work for you rather than somebody else.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Description">Find the Mavros who are building the pirate fighter/bomber technology. Bring along a generous bribe, and you might be able to convince them to work for you…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Objective">Search the indicated Curiosity $CuriosityPlanetName on the planet  with $Amount01Name of [Strat04anti-matterColored]  #EB897C#Antimatter#REVERT# -- but hurry. It's winner-takes-all!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-ObjectiveTooltip">Search the Curiosity when you are ready to pay  $Amount01Name of  [Strat04anti-matterColored]  #EB897C#Antimatter#REVERT#.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Outcome">Well, that was interesting. The Mavros weren't even bothered when your armada showed up at their orbital station; they figured you were just another customer. Now the engineers and their tech is yours--it's time to exploit your investment!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalQuest09-Compet-Failed">Something has gone wrong… Either another Empire beat you to it, or somebody was angry enough to destroy the planet! Regardless, you will not be able to uncover the secret of the Mavros technology.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Title">A Factory of One's Own</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Description">As it turns out, the Mavros had set up quite an impressive "clean" facility on their orbital station. They were happy to leave it behind, however, as they had reached the limit of what they could do with the station's resources--and besides, luxury shipments were rare. Now that the fiscal and technical weight of your empire is behind them, they can start developing the next generation of their technology.
It all starts with a new site and a new facility, generously funded by you, and staffed by them. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Choice01Description">In order to get the most out of the Mavros engineers and their technology, you will need to build a new Improvement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Choice01Objective">Build the Mavros Skunkworks System Improvement on Empire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Choice01ObjectiveTooltip">This is a unique Improvement (one per empire)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExplorationQuest23Choice01Outcome">The work is impressive. For all their reputation as crazed troublemakers, when they are focused and sober the Mavros are superlative engineers. Your fleets will profit from the new factory, and your finest tacticians have already worked out dangerous new battle plans.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroPirate01Title">Bosun Jennifer Rach</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroPirate01Description">Rach was part of a pirate band who broke into an Endless research station and were promptly caught by the security systems. A passing Amoeba ship caught their distress signal, but by the time the Amoeba arrived a Dust-enhanced Rach had already freed her team, cracked the research station lock, looted it, and augmented their ship. As the Amoeba were headed to the Academy she decided to go with them, in spite of the pleas of her heartbroken partner, Sego, and her angry boss, Nico the Psycho, who viewed her skills as a ticket to riches. Thanks to her skills with flight technology, she has since made a name for herself as an inventor and test pilot of new and improbable craft and their uses in battle. It is whispered that even though she has the training of the Academy, deep down she still has the heart of a buccaneer…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MinorFactionPiratesTitle">Pirates</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MinorFactionPiratesDescription">The universe is full of wealth and riches, and there are those who would rather take what has already been created than do the hard work themselves. While military expeditions generally destroy these bands of pirates or raiders before they become too powerful, one syndicate of pirate-traders, known as ABC (the Autonomous Bastards' Collective), has grown sufficiently large and wealthy to constitute a serious threat to galactic development. Diplomacy and interaction may be required to control them, and an enterprising few may figure out ways to harness their mercenary lust...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestGlobalCompet09Title">Mavros Skunkworks</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestGlobalCompet09Description">As tradition demands they are unofficial, off-budget, and highly effective. The Mavros engineers working in this apparently nondescript factory and lab are tasked with developing new military-industrial technology. If explosions are a reliable measure, they are doing wonderfully.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayPostLongShipRepairWithSquadronTitle">Repair Protocol</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayPostLongShipRepairWithSquadronDescription">Post-battle, surviving Squadron crews aid in the repair of their damaged host Ship</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayPostLongShipRepairWithSquadronTooltip">Any Ship with surviving Squadron Modules repairs by X per Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveBalancedSquadronOffenseBoostTitle">Strafing Run</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveBalancedSquadronOffenseBoostDescription">These orders ensure that the fighters' primary role is bomber protection, focusing on the destruction of enemy fighters intercepting bombers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveBalancedSquadronOffenseBoostTooltip">All Fighters escort Bombers 
+10% critical attack probability on Fighters &amp; Bombers</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveMediumSquadronDefenseBoostTitle">Fleet Escort</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveMediumSquadronDefenseBoostDescription">Rather than going on the attack, fighters are ordered to defend the fleet vessels. Their familairity with the ships and maneuvers give them improved odds to dodge attacks.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveMediumSquadronDefenseBoostTooltip">All Fighters escort friendly Ships
+10% dodge probability on Fighters &amp; Bombers</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveShortDamageReductionPerSquadronTitle">For the Cause</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveShortDamageReductionPerSquadronDescription">Fighters and Bombers are used as cannon fodder, drawing enemy fire and improving the survival odds of the larger ships in the fleet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayDefensiveShortDamageReductionPerSquadronTooltip">-50% max Health on Squadrons
+1% damage reduction to Fleet per Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveMediumSquadronDamageIncreasePerSquadronTitle">Wing Coordination</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveMediumSquadronDamageIncreasePerSquadronDescription">By sharing data and analyses in real time between squadrons, they gain notable tactical advantages over their enemies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayOffensiveMediumSquadronDamageIncreasePerSquadronTooltip">+1% damage by Squadrons per Squadron in Fleet </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AdvancedPlayModalWindowFighterDistributionTitle">[fighter] Fighter Formations: {0} [offensiveMilitaryPower] / {1} [defensiveMilitaryPower]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AdvancedPlayModalWindowFighterDistributionDescription">[offensiveMilitaryPower] Offensive Fighters escort your Bombers and assault enemy Ships
[defensiveMilitaryPower] Defensive Fighters escort your Ships


The same Battle Tactics' families share the same [fighter] Fighter formations</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CategoryModuleSquadronTitle">Squadron Module</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubCategoryModuleSquadronFighterTitle">Fighter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubCategoryModuleSquadronBomberTitle">Bomber</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEffectsSquadronMaximumHealthTitle">Health</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEffectsSquadronBaseUnitsCountTitle">Units in Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEffectsSquadronDodgeChanceTitle">Dodge probability</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEffectsSquadronCriticalAttackChanceTitle">Critical attack probability</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEffectsSquadronTitle">Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseBonusOverallTitle">Defense bonus</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassModuleSquadronTitle">Squadron</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassModuleSquadronMultipleTitle">Squadrons</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CriticalAttackChanceTitle">Critical Attack probability</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DodgeChanceTitle">Dodge probability</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementPlayDeck7Title">Lethal Squadrons</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementPlayDeck7Description">These tactics will enhance squadron capabilities in battlefield encounters.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairAfterBattleIfSurvivingSquadronTitle">Ship repair if surviving Squadrons</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FlakEvasionSquadronTitle">Squadron Flak Evasion</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayEffectSquadronOffenseBoostTooltipEffect">All Fighters escort Bombers and assault enemy Ships</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlayEffectSquadronDefenseBoostTooltipEffect">All Fighters escort Ships</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EncounterFighterBomberFighterDescription">Number of operational Fighter units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EncounterFighterBomberDeadFighterDescription">Number of destroyed Fighter units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EncounterFighterBomberBomberDescription">Number of operational Bomber units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EncounterFighterBomberDeadBomberDescription">Number of destroyed Bomber units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberTitlePlayer">Damage caused by Bomber units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberDescriptionPlayer">The Bombers' main objective is to cause massive damage to enemy ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberTitleCriticalPlayer">Damage caused by your Bomber units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#
Including #E3BDAC#{1}#REVERT# critical damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberDescriptionCriticalPlayer">The Bombers' main objective is to cause massive damage to enemy ships.
Critical attacks double the damage Bombers deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberTitleEnemy">Damage caused by enemy Bomber units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberDescriptionEnemy">The enemy Bombers' main objective is to cause massive damage to your ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberTitleCriticalEnemy">Damage caused by enemy Bomber units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#
Including #E3BDAC#{1}#REVERT# critical damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByBomberDescriptionCriticalEnemy">The enemy Bombers' main objective is to cause massive damage to your ships.
Critical attacks double the damage Bombers deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterTitlePlayer">Damage caused by friendly Fighter units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterDescriptionPlayer">Fighters protect your ships from enemy Bombers. Alternatively, they escort and protect your Bombers while they execute their missions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterTitleCriticalPlayer">Damage caused by your Fighter units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#
Including #E3BDAC#{1}#REVERT# critical damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterDescriptionCriticalPlayer">Fighters protect your ships from enemy Bombers. Alternatively, they escort and protect your Bombers while they execute their missions.
Critical attacks double the damage Fighters deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterTitleEnemy">Damage caused by enemy Fighter units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterDescriptionEnemy">Fighters protect enemy ships from your Bomber attacks. Alternatively, they escort and protect enemy Bombers while they execute their mission.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterTitleCriticalEnemy">Damage caused by enemy Fighter units: #E3BDAC#{0}#REVERT#
Including #E3BDAC#{1}#REVERT# critical damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageAppliedByFighterDescriptionCriticalEnemy">Fighters protect enemy ships from your Bomber attacks. Alternatively, they escort and protect enemy Bombers while they execute their mission.
Critical attacks double the damage Fighters deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnologyDefinitionQuestFB01Title">Mavros Methodology</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnologyDefinitionQuestFB01Description">Unorthodox, dangerous, aggressive, and full of shortcuts, Mavros scientific methods are highly effective if the scientists and engineers survive.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestFB01Title">Portable N-Way Qcomms</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestFB01Description">While quantum communication between two nodes is relatively well understood, this technology uses multiple related reactions to allow quantum communications between multiple connected sites simultaneously.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestFB01TooltipEffect">Unlock "Wing Coordination" Battle Tactic</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleScreenSquadronAttackStartEventTitle">Start Squadron Attack</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>